{
    "id": "86bd61e645614536ab196b0468e165c9",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was so angry the ………………………. stood out on his forehead.",
            "description": "Vein means blood vessel. ",
            "answers": [
                "vains",
                "veins",
                "vanes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1325e350247841e1b22b73df49ea9d64"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rescuers made a ……………………. attempt to reach the sinking boat.",
            "description": "Vain means futile or useless.",
            "answers": [
                "vein",
                "vain",
                "vane"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8cae81198bcb4612bac0c9f6d59ae917"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………… politician had no thought of the public welfare.",
            "description": "Venal means corrupt.",
            "answers": [
                "venal",
                "venial"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6de9e2c3da434b70b2592d87c7ab31db"
        },
        {
            "question": "His new ………………………….. doesn’t fit well.",
            "description": "A suit is a coat with matching trousers or shirt.",
            "answers": [
                "suit",
                "suite",
                "soot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c35cd8233ae41d9985f1f8d9f2d428d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Reserve the bridal ……………………….. at the hotel.",
            "description": "A suite is a set of related rooms.",
            "answers": [
                "soot",
                "suit",
                "suite"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "78062864b26046c587f1cf1ec4c9d34d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke to the audience in a humorous ………………………",
            "description": "A vane is a direction pointer. Vein can mean mood.",
            "answers": [
                "vain",
                "vein",
                "vane"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e289e16eb1e4b80ae60936a4707bff9"
        },
        {
            "question": "A …………………….. sin does not keep one out of Heaven.",
            "description": "Venial means pardonable.",
            "answers": [
                "venial",
                "venal"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0940fcfda21c4803893f6f7a00ee2af3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Waterloo is a ……………………….. battleground.",
            "description": "Historic means famous in history.",
            "answers": [
                "historic",
                "historical"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50f679f010324956b5e79d68c231b7ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a …………………………. fact that George Washington had false teeth made of wood.",
            "description": "Historical means concerned with history, recorded or chronicled. ",
            "answers": [
                "historic",
                "historical"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f51a9635fad9480dbe9f9b37e676a8aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very ………………………… about her appearance.",
            "description": "Vain means proud, too concerned or arrogant.",
            "answers": [
                "vain",
                "vein",
                "vane"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6cf3c818f76d4784b0d1e5eb81e3e534"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………………. of food was found in the cave.",
            "description": "A hoard means a stockpile. ",
            "answers": [
                "hoard",
                "horde"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6fe3a902e521449594f719c73db2c8eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………………… of Tatars invaded Europe.",
            "description": "Horde means a crowd.",
            "answers": [
                "horde",
                "hoard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0502ba6c85264eb29868ef209379f256"
        }
    ]
}